wbls.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy - Emmis Communications Emmis Communications

English | **E _s_ pañol**

**Privacy Policy**

Last modified: June 12, 2018

  1. **Introduction**

Emmis Operating Company and its affiliates (collectively “Company,” “We,” or “Us”) respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through compliance with this policy (Privacy Policy).

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit this website, through which you accessed this Privacy Policy (Website) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On this Website.
  * In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * Us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party.
  * Any third party, including through any application or content that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

  2. **Children Under the Age of 13**

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features/register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13, we will delete that information (including any associated profile) to the extent that it is in a system we control. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at the email address listed at the end of this Privacy Policy.

  3. **Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It**

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

  * By which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, username and password, phone number, and date of birth (“personal information”).
  * About your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies.

  4. **_Information You Provide to Us_**

The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

  * Information that you provide by registering for our Website, including through any social media platform through which you register. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website or such information that is designated as public information through any social media platform through which you register for our Website. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, fill out a survey, and when you report a problem with our Website.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us.
  * Your search queries on the Website.
  * Any other information that you permit a social media platform to share with our Website.

To the extent permitted by the Website, you also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “posted”) on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, “User Contributions”). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

  5. **_Usage Details, IP Addresses And Cookies/, Cookies and Other Technologies_**

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may automatically collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type.

The information we collect automatically is statistical data, and does not identify any individual. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.
  * Understand which parts of the Website to optimize based on user traffic.
  * Provide targeted advertising or relevant content.
  * Provide only news and information relevant to usage data.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
  * **Flash Cookies.** Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies.
  * **Web Beacons.** Pages of our the Website may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs. pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).
  * **Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.**

  6. **Third-party Advertiser Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Some advertisements on the Website may be served by third-party advertisers, ad networks and ad servers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about our users. This may include information about users’ behavior on this and other websites to serve them interested-based (behavioral) advertising. We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement, you should contact the responsible advertiser directly.

  7. **How We Use Your Information**

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To provide you with notices about your account/subscription, including expiration and renewal notices.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website.
  * To process and deliver contest entries and rewards.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, you may opt out by (i) modifying your registered user information on the Website by logging in, editing your profile preferences and following the directions to opt out, or (ii) following the removal instructions in the communication that you receive. We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

  8. **Disclosure of Your Information**

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this Privacy Policy:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of Emmis Operating Companys assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Emmis Operating Company about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Emmis Operating Company, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

  9. **C** **hoices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information**

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
  * **Promotional Offers from the Company.** If you do not wish to have your e-mail address used by the Company to promote our own or third parties’ products or services, you may opt out by modifying your registered user information on the Website by logging in, editing your profile preferences and following the directions to opt out. You may also unsubscribe by using the link in the email message you received.
  * **Targeted Advertising.** If you do not want us to use information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements according to our advertisers’ target-audience preferences, you may opt out by modifying your registered user information on the Website by logging in, editing your profile preferences and following the directions to opt out.

We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However, these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) on the NAI’s website.

  * **Geographic** If you do not want us to collect information regarding your geographic location, you can disable geographic location tracking by adjusting your devices settings or by declining such tracking when prompted. Note that some services may no longer work as a result of disabling location tracking.
  * **Digital Advertising Alliance Consumer Choice**. You may opt out of behavioral advertising delivered by the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) through the DAA Consumer Choice Page located at <https://www.aboutads.info/choices/>.

  10. **Accessing and Correcting Your Information**

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page.

You may send us an e-mail at the email address listed at the end of this Privacy Policy to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect. Any user account that remains inactive for at least one (1) year may be deleted by Company.

If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our Terms of Use.

  11. **California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to the email address listed at the end of this Privacy Policy. We do not respond to Do Not Track browser signals.

  12. **Data Security**

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to take reasonable precautions to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

  13. **Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Privacy Policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you by e-mail to the e-mail address specified in your account or through a notice on the Website home page. The date the Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of this policy. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this Privacy Policy to check for any changes.

  14. **Your Comments and Concerns**

This Website is operated by Emmis Operating Company or its affiliates, One EMMIS Plaza, 40 Monument Circle, Suite 700, Indianapolis, IN 46204.

All feedback, comments, requests for technical support, and other communications relating to the Website should be directed to the contact set forth below for this Website.

  15. **_Website Contact Information:_**

To contact the Website, you may send communications to:

Emmis Digital Support  
401 North Franklin Street, Suite 5s  
Chicago, Illinois 60654

**Política de Privacidad **

Última modificación: 13 de junio de 2018 

**1\. Introducción  
**

Emmis Operating Company y sus afilados (colectivamente Compañía, Nosotros, o Nos) respetan su privacidad y están comprometidos a protegerla mediante el cumplimiento con esta política (Política de Privacidad). 

Esta política describe los tipos de información que podemos recopilar de usted o que usted puede proporcionar cuando visite este sitio web, a través del cual usted accedióa esta Política de Privacidad (Sitio Web) y nuestras prácticas para recopilar, usar, mantener, proteger y divulgar esa información. 

Esta política se aplica a la información que recopilamos: 

  * En este Sitio Web. 
  * En el correo electrónico, mensajes de texto y otros mensajes electrónicos entre usted y este Sitio Web.

La política no se aplica a la información recopilada por:

  * Nosotros fuera de línea o a través de otros medios, incluyendo cualquier otro sitio web operado por la Compañía o cualquier tercero.
  * Cualquier tercero, incluyendo cualquier aplicación o contenido que pueda enlazarse o ser accesible desde o en el Sitio Web.

Por favor lea con detenimiento esta política para entender nuestras políticas y prácticas con respecto a su información y cómo la utilizaremos. Si no está de acuerdo con nuestras políticas y prácticas, su opción es no usar nuestro Sitio Web. Al acceder o usar este Sitio Web, usted acepta esta Política de Privacidad. Esta política puede cambiar de vez en cuando. Su uso continuo de este Sitio Web, después de que hagamos cambios, se considera una aceptación de esos cambios, de manera que debe revisar la política periódicamente para ver las actualizaciones.

**2\. Niños menores de 13 años de edad**

Nuestro Sitio Web no está diseñado para niños menores de 13 años de edad. Ninguna persona menor de 13 años de edad puede proporcionar ningún tipo de información personal al o en el Sitio Web. Nosotros no recopilamos intencionalmente la información personal de niños menores de 13 años de edad. Si usted es menor de 13 años de edad, no utilice ni proporcione información alguna en este Sitio Web o en o a través de sus funciones/registro en el Sitio Web, no efectúe ninguna compra a través del Sitio Web, no utilice ninguna de las funciones de comentarios públicos o interactivos de este Sitio Web ni suministre ninguna información sobre usted, incluyendo su nombre, dirección, número telefónico, correo electrónico o cualquier nombre de pantalla o de usuario que pueda utilizar. Si detectamos que hemos recopilado o recibido información personal de un niño menor de 13 años de edad, borraremos esa información (incluido cualquier perfil asociado) en la medida en que esté en un sistema que controlemos. Si cree que pudiéramos tener alguna información de o sobre un niño menor de 13 años de edad, contáctenos al correo electrónico que se indica al final de esta Política de Privacidad. 

**3\. Información que recopilamos sobre usted y cómo la recopilamos  
**

Recopilamos diversos tipos de información de y sobre los usuarios de nuestro Sitio Web, que incluye información: 

  * Mediante la cual se le puede identificar personalmente, como el nombre, dirección postal, dirección de correo electrónico, nombre de usuario y contraseña, número telefónico y fecha de nacimiento (información personal).
  * Sobre su conexión a internet, el equipo que usa para acceder a nuestro Sitio Web y datos de uso.

Recopilamos esta información:

* Directamente de usted cuando nos la suministra.
* Automáticamente mientras navega en el sitio. La información recopilada automáticamente puede incluir datos de uso, direcciones IP e información recopilada a través de cookies, web beacons y otras tecnologías de seguimiento. 

**4\. Información que usted nos proporciona**

La información que recopilamos en o a través de nuestro Sitio Web puede incluir:

  * Información que usted proporcione al registrarse en nuestro Sitio Web, incluyendo cualquier plataforma de redes sociales a través de la cual usted se registre. Esto incluye información suministrada al momento de registrarse para usar nuestro Sitio Web o la información que es designada como información pública en cualquier plataforma de redes sociales mediante la cual usted se registra para usar nuestro Sitio Web. También podemos pedirle información cuando ingrese a un concurso o promoción patrocinada por nosotros, llene una encuesta y cuando informe sobre un problema con nuestro Sitio Web.
  * Registros y copias de su correspondencia (incluidos los correos electrónicos), si nos contacta.
  * Sus términos de búsqueda en el Sitio Web.
  * Cualquier otra información que usted le permita a una plataforma de redes social compartir con nuestro Sitio Web.

En la medida permitida por el Sitio Web, usted también puede suministrar información que se publicará o exhibirá (en lo sucesivo, publicar) en áreas públicas del Sitio Web, o transmitidas a otros usuarios del Sitio Web o terceros (colectivamente, Contribuciones del Usuario). Sus Contribuciones de Usuario se publican en y se transmiten a otros a su propio riesgo. Tenga en cuenta que ninguna medida de seguridad es perfecta o impenetrable. Además, no podemos controlar las acciones de otros usuarios del Sitio Web con quienes usted elija compartir sus Contribuciones de Usuario. Por lo tanto, no podemos y no garantizamos que sus Contribuciones de Usuario no serán vistas por personas no autorizadas.

**5\. Datos de uso, direcciones IP y Cookies/, Cookies y otras tecnologías**

A medida que usted navegue e interactúe con nuestro Sitio Web, automáticamente podemos recopilar información sobre su equipo, acciones y patrones de navegación, que incluye: 

  * Detalles de sus visitas a nuestro Sitio Web, incluyendo datos de tráfico, datos de ubicación y otros datos de comunicación y los recursos a los que accede y usa en el Sitio Web.
  * Información sobre su computadora y conexión a internet, incluyendo su dirección IP, sistema operativo y tipo de navegador.

La información que recopilamos automáticamente son datos estadísticos y no identifican a ningún individuo. Nos ayuda a mejorar nuestro Sitio Web y a brindar mejores servicios y más personalizados al permitirnos:

  * Estimar el tamaño de nuestra audiencia y patrones de uso.
  * Almacenar información sobre sus preferencias, permitiéndonos personalizar nuestro Sitio Web de acuerdo a sus intereses individuales.
  * Acelerar sus búsquedas.
  * Reconocerlo cuando regrese a nuestro Sitio Web.
  * Entender qué partes optimizar del Sitio Web basado en el tráfico de usuario.
  * Proporcionar publicidad personalizada o contenido relevante.
  * Proporcionar solo noticias e información relevantes a los datos de uso.

Las tecnologías que usamos para esta recopilación automática de datos pueden incluir:

  * **Cookies (o cookies de navegador).** Una cookie es un archivo pequeño colocado en el disco duro de su computadora. Usted puede negarse a aceptar las cookies de navegador al activar la configuración correspondiente en su navegador. Sin embargo, si usted selecciona esta configuración, usted no podrá acceder a ciertas partes de nuestro Sitio Web. A menos que haya ajustado la configuración de su navegador de manera que rechace las cookies, nuestro sistema emitirá cookies cuando use su navegador para ingresar a nuestro Sitio Web. 
  * **Cookies en Flash.** Ciertas funciones de nuestros Sitio Web pueden usar objetos almacenados localmente (o cookies en Flash) para recopilar y almacenar información sobre sus preferencias y navegación hacia, desde y en nuestro Sitio Web. Las Flash cookies no se administran con las mismas configuraciones de navegador que se utilizan para las cookies de navegador. 
  * **Web Beacons.** Las páginas de nuestro Sitio Web pueden contener archivos electrónicos pequeños conocidos como web beacons (también se les conoce como clear gifs. pixel tags y single-pixel gifs) que le permiten a la Compañía, por ejemplo, contar los usuarios que han visitado esas páginas o para otras estadísticas relacionadas con el sitio web (por ejemplo, registrar la popularidad de cierto contenido del sitio web y verificar la integridad del sistema y el servidor). 
  * **Google Informes de intereses y datos demográficos.**

**6\. Uso de cookies y otras tecnologías de seguimiento para publicidad de terceros**

Alguna publicidad en el Sitio Web puede ser presentada por terceros publicistas, redes de publicidad y servidores de publicidad. Estos terceros pueden utilizar cookies solas o junto con web beacons u otras tecnologías de seguimiento para recopilar información sobre nuestros usuarios. Esto puede incluir información sobre la conducta de los usuarios en este y otros sitios web para prestar un servicio basado en la publicidad que les interesa (conductual). Nosotros no controlamos estas tecnologías de seguimiento de terceros o cómo pueden ser utilizadas. Si tiene preguntas sobre una publicidad, debe comunicarse directamente con el publicista responsable. 

**7\. Cómo usamos su información**

Usamos la información que recopilamos sobre usted o que usted nos proporciona, incluyendo cualquier información personal, para: 

  * Presentarle nuestro Sitio Web y su contenido a usted.
  * Proporcionarle información, productos o servicios que usted nos solicite.
  * Cumplir cualquier otro propósito para el cual usted la proporciona.
  * Entregarle notificaciones sobre su cuenta/suscripción, incluyendo notificaciones.
  * Cumplir con nuestras obligaciones y hacer cumplir nuestros derechos producto de cualquier contrato celebrado entre usted y nosotros, incluyendo la facturación y cobro.
  * Notificarle sobre los cambios a nuestro Sitio Web o cualquier producto o servicio que ofrecemos o brindamos a través del sitio.
  * Permitirle participar en las funciones interactivas de nuestro Sitio Web.
  * Procesar e ingresar entradas y premios de concursos.
  * Poder describir de otra manera cuando usted proporciona la información.
  * Cualquier otro fin con su consentimiento.

También podemos usar su información para comunicarnos con usted con respecto a nuestros propios bienes y servicios que puedan ser de su interés. Si no desea que usemos su información de esta manera, usted puede retirarse al (i) modificar su información de usuario registrada en el Sitio Web iniciando sesión, editando las preferencias de su perfil y siguiendo las instrucciones para retirarse, o (ii) siguiendo las instrucciones de retiro en la comunicación que usted recibe. Podemos usar la información que hemos recopilado de usted para permitirnos mostrar publicidad a nuestras audiencias objetivo de los anunciantes. Aunque nosotros no divulgamos su información personal para estos fines sin su consentimiento, si hace clic o de algún otro modo interactúa con una publicidad, el anunciante puede asumir que usted cumple con sus criterios de audiencia. 

**8\. Divulgación de su información**

Podemos divulgar información agregado sobre nuestros usuarios e información que no identifica a ningún individuo, sin restricción. 

Podemos divulgar información que recopilemos o que usted proporcione según lo descrito en esta Política de Privacidad: 

  * A nuestras subsidiarias y afiliados.
  * A contratistas, proveedores de servicio y otros terceros que utilizamos para apoyar nuestro negocio y que están vinculados por obligaciones contractuales a mantener la confidencialidad de la información personal y usarla solo para los fines para los cuales se las revelamos a ellos.
  * A un comprador u otro sucesor en caso de fusión, desinversión, reestructuración, reorganización, disolución u otra venta o transferencia de algunos o todos los activos de Emmis Operating Company, ya sea como una empresa en marcha o como parte de una quiebra, liquidación o similares en la que la información personal de la empresa Emmis sobre los usuarios de nuestro Sitio Web se encuentra entre los activos transferidos. 
  * Para cumplir el propósito para el cual usted la proporciona. 
  * Para cualquier otro fin divulgado por nosotros cuando usted proporciona la información.
  * Con su consentimiento.

También podemos divulgar su información personal:

  * Para cumplir con alguna orden judicial, la ley o proceso legal, incluso para responder a una solicitud gubernamental o regulatoria.
  * Para cumplir o aplicar nuestros términos de uso y otros acuerdos, incluso para fines de facturación y cobranza.
  * Si consideramos que la divulgación es necesaria o adecuada para proteger derechos, la propiedad o seguridad de Emmis Operating Company, nuestros clientes u otros. Esto incluye el intercambio de información con otras compañías y organizaciones con fines de protección contra el fraude y reducción de riesgo de crédito.

**9\. Opciones sobre cómo usamos y divulgamos su información**

Nos esforzamos por proporcionarle opciones con respecto a la información personal que nos proporcione. Hemos creado mecanismos para proporcionarle el siguiente control sobre su información: 

  * **Tecnologías de seguimiento y publicidad.** Puede configurar su navegador para rechazar todas o algunas cookies del navegador o para avisarle cuando se envían las cookies. Para obtener más información sobre cómo administrar la configuración de las cookies en Flash, visite la página de configuración de Flash Player en el sitio web de Adobe. Si desactiva o rechaza las cookies, tenga en cuenta que algunas partes de este sitio pueden ser inaccesibles o no funcionar correctamente.
  * **Ofertas promocionales de la Compañía.** Si no desea que su dirección de correo electrónico sea utilizada por la Compañía para promocionar productos o servicios propios o de terceros, puede retirarse al modificar su información de usuario registrada en el Sitio Web iniciando sesión, editando sus preferencias de perfil y siguiendo las instrucciones para no participar. También puede retirar la suscripción mediante el enlace del mensaje de correo electrónico que recibió.
  * **Publicidad dirigida.** Si no desea que utilicemos la información que recopilamos o que nos proporcione para publicar anuncios de acuerdo con las preferencias del público objetivo de nuestros anunciantes, puede retirarse al modificar su información de usuario registrada en el Sitio Web iniciando sesión, editando sus preferencias de perfil y siguiendo las instrucciones para retirarse. 

No controlamos la recopilación o el uso de su información por terceros para publicar anuncios basados en intereses. Sin embargo, estos terceros pueden proporcionarle formas de elegir para que su información no sea recopilada o utilizada de esta manera. Usted puede optar por no recibir anuncios de los miembros de la Iniciativa de Publicidad en Red (Network Advertising Initiative, NAI) en el sitio web de NAI. 

  * **Ubicación geográfica.** Si no desea que recopilemos información sobre su ubicación geográfica, puede deshabilitar el seguimiento de ubicación geográfica ajustando la configuración de su dispositivo o rechazando dicho seguimiento cuando se le solicite. Tenga en cuenta que algunos servicios pueden dejar de funcionar como resultado de deshabilitar el seguimiento de ubicación. 
  * **Opción del consumidor de la Alianza de Publicidad Digital.** Usted puede optar por no participar en publicidad de comportamiento entregada por la Alianza de Publicidad Digital (Digital Advertising Alliance, DAA) a través de la página de DAA Consumer Choice ubicada en <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>. 

**10\. Acceder a su información y corregirla**

Puede revisar y cambiar su información personal iniciando sesión en el Sitio Web y visitando su página del perfil de la cuenta. 

Puede enviarnos un correo electrónico a la dirección de correo electrónico que aparece al final de esta Política de Privacidad para solicitar acceso, corregir o eliminar cualquier información personal que nos haya proporcionado. No podemos eliminar su información personal, excepto que también borremos su cuenta de usuario. Es posible que no aceptemos una solicitud de cambio de información si creemos que el cambio violaría cualquier ley o requisito legal o hará que la información sea incorrecta. Cualquier cuenta de usuario que permanezca inactiva durante por lo menos un año puede ser eliminada por la Compañia. 

Si elimina las Contribuciones de Usuario del Sitio Web, las copias de sus Contribuciones de Usuario pueden permanecer visibles en páginas almacenadas en caché y archivadas, o pueden haber sido copiadas o almacenadas por otros usuarios del Sitio Web. El acceso adecuado y el uso de la información proporcionada en el Sitio web, incluyendo las Contribuciones del Usuario, se rigen por nuestros Términos de Uso. 

**11\. Derechos de Privacidad de California**

La sección 1798.83 del Código Civil de California les permite a los usuarios de nuestro Sitio Web que sean residentes de California solicitar cierta información con respecto a nuestra divulgación de información personal a terceros para sus propósitos de marketing directo. Para hacer tal solicitud, envíe un correo electrónico a la dirección de correo electrónico que aparece al final de esta Política de Privacidad. No respondemos a las señales del navegador de No rastrear. 

**12\. Seguridad de datos**

Hemos implementado medidas diseñadas para proteger su información personal de pérdida accidental y de acceso, uso, alteración y divulgación no autorizados. Toda la información que nos proporciona se almacena en nuestros servidores seguros detrás de cortafuegos. 

La seguridad de su información también depende de usted. Donde le hemos dado (o donde usted ha elegido) una contraseña para acceder a ciertas partes de nuestro Sitio Web, usted es responsable de mantener esta contraseña confidencial. Le pedimos que no comparta su contraseña con nadie. Le instamos a que sea cuidadoso en dar información en áreas públicas del Sitio Web como tableros de mensajes. La información que usted comparte en las áreas públicas puede ser vista por cualquier usuario del Sitio Web. 

Desafortunadamente, la transmisión de información a través de Internet no es completamente segura. Aunque hacemos todo lo posible para tomar las precauciones razonables para proteger su información personal, no podemos garantizar la seguridad de su información personal transmitida a nuestro Sitio Web. Cualquier transmisión de información personal es bajo su propio riesgo. No somos responsables de eludir cualquier configuración de privacidad o medidas de seguridad contenidas en el Sitio Web. 

**13\. Cambios a nuestra Política de Privacidad**

Es nuestra política publicar cualquier cambio que hagamos a nuestra Política de Privacidad en esta página. Si realizamos cambios materiales en la forma en que tratamos la información personal de nuestros usuarios, le notificaremos por correo electrónico a la dirección de correo electrónico especificada en su cuenta o a través de un aviso en la página principal del Sitio Web. La fecha en que se revisópor última vez la Política de Privacidad se encuentra en la parte superior de esta política. Usted es responsable de garantizar que tengamos una dirección de correo electrónico activa y entregable actualizada para usted, y de visitar periódicamente nuestro Sitio Web y esta Política de Privacidad para comprobar si hay algún cambio. 

**14\. Sus comentarios e inquietudes**

Este Sitio Web es operado por Emmis Operating Company o sus afiliados, One EMMIS Plaza, 40 Monument Circle, Suite 700, Indianapolis, IN 46204. 

Todas las opiniones, comentarios, solicitudes de soporte técnico y otras comunicaciones relacionadas con el Sitio Web deben dirigirse a los contactos que se indican a continuación para este Sitio Web. 

**15\. Información de contacto del Sitio Web:**  
Para contactar al Sitio Web, puede enviar comunicaciones a:
